Guide to the New York University Archives Audiovisual Collection AV
New York University Archives
- Audiovisual Recordings
  - Urban League Presents: Organizing Minority Workers, 1960; AV447 (Box 11, Reel 447)
  - Urban League Presents: Problems of Slum Clearance, Part 1, 1960; AV448; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.) (Box 11, Reel 448)
  - Urban League Presents: Integration in Public Housing, 1960; AV450 (Box 11, Reel 450)
  - Urban League Presents: Your Social Security, Part 1, 1960; AV451 (Box 11, Reel 451, Box Shared University Archives 117, Item 5)
  - Urban League Presents: Your Social Security, Part 2, 1960; AV452 (Box 11, Reel 452, Box Shared University Archives 117, Item 4)
  - Urban League Presents: Employment Discrimination in N.Y.C., 1960; AV453 (Box 157, Reel 453)
  - Urban League Presents: Shakespeare in Harlem, 1960; AV454 (Box 157, Reel 454)
  - Urban League Presents: The Need for Improving Minimum Wage Standards in N.Y.C., 1960; AV455 (Box 157, Reel 455, Box Shared University Archives 117, Item 3)
  - Urban League Presents: You and Your Parents' Association, 1960; AV456 (Box 157, Reel 456)
  - Urban League Presents: Is There a Puerto Rican Problem?, 1959-1960; AV457 (Box 11, Reel 457)
    Puerto Rico.; Puerto Ricans.
  - Urban League Presents: Your Workman's Compensation, 1960; AV458 (Box 157, Reel 458)
  - Urban League Presents: You and Unemployment Insurance, 1960; AV459 (Box 157, Reel 459)
  - Urban League Presents: Protest, Part 1, 1960; AV460 (Box 157, Reel 460, Box Shared University Archives 117, Item 2)
  - Urban League Presents: Protest, Part 2, 1960; AV461 (Box 157, Reel 461, Box Shared University Archives 117, Item 1)
  - Urban League Presents: Let's Be Human, 1960; AV462 (Box 157, Reel 462, Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 40)
  - Urban League Presents: The Negro Artist, Part 1, 1960; AV463 (Box 123, Reel 463)
  - Urban League Presents: The Negro Artist, Part 2, 1960; AV464 (Box 123, Reel 464)
  - Urban League Presents: Is There Discrimination in Auto Insurance?, 1960; AV465 (Box 123, Reel 465)
  - Urban League Presents: How to Organize a Rent Clinic, Part 1, 1960; AV466 (Box 123, Reel 466)
  - Urban League Presents: How to Organize a Rent Clinic, Part 2, 1960; AV467 (Box 157, Reel 467)
  - Urban League Presents: A Realtor Looks at Bigotry, 1960; AV468 (Box 123, Reel 468)
  - Urban League Presents: Homes for Homeless Children, Part 1, 1960; AV469 (Box 12, Reel 469)
    Homelessness
  - Urban League Presents: Homes for Homeless Children, Part 2, 1960; AV470 (Box 12, Reel 470)
  - Urban League Presents: A Program for School Integration, Part 1, 1960; AV471 (Box 157, Reel 471)
  - Odyssey of Runyon Jones, The, June 8, 1941; cuid17540 (Box 157, Reel AV_449)
  - Urban League Presents: Luxury Housing and Tenant Evictions, Part 1, 1961; AV472 (Box 12, Reel 472)
  - Urban League Presents: Luxury Housing and Tenant Evictions, Part 2, 1961 February 12; AV473; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 videocartridges 14:23 (Box 12, Reel 473)
  - Urban League Presents: Be a Friend to a Boy, 1961 February 19; AV474; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels 14:29 (Box 12, Reel 474)
  - Urban League Presents: Cancer Prevention, 1961 February 26; AV475; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 475)
    Cancer
  - Urban League Presents: The American Negro Looks at Africa, 1961 March 5; AV476; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels 14:26 (Box 12, Reel 476)
    Africa
  - Urban League Presents: The Sharkey Brown Isaacs Law Effective, 1961 March 12; AV477; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14 minutes (Box 12, Reel 477)
  - Urban League Presents: The Press and the Community, 1961 March 19; AV478; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14 minutes (Box 12, Reel 478)
  - Urban League Presents: Call Me By My Rightful Name, 1961 March 26; AV479; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 15 minutes (Box 12, Reel 479)
  - Urban League Presents: Hardship Rent Increases, 1961; AV480; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 480)
  - Urban League Presents: Building Private Interracial Housing, 1961 April 9; AV481; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels 14:24 (Box 12, Reel 481)
  - Urban League Presents: Do Negro G.I.'s Become Second-Class Veterans, Part 1, 1961 April 16; AV482; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 482)
  - Urban League Presents: Do Negro G.I.'s Become Second-Class Veterans?, Part 2, 1961 April 23; AV483; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 483)
  - Urban League Presents: Teenage Gangs, 1961 July 30; AV484; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 484)
  - Urban League Presents: Community Hospitals in New York City, 1961 August 6; AV485; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 485)
  - Urban League Presents: Conquest of Tensions, Part 1, 1961 August 13; AV486; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 486)
  - Urban League Presents: Conquest of Tensions, Part 2, 1961 August 20; AV487; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 487)
  - Urban League Presents: Stay in School, 1961 August 27; AV488; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 41, Box 12, Reel 488)
  - Urban League Presents: The Future of Labor Management Relations, 1961 September 3; AV489; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 489)
  - Urban League Presents: How to Spot a Bigot, 1961 September 10; AV490; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 490)
  - Urban League Presents: Should City Employees Join Unions?, 1961 September 17; AV491; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 491)
  - Urban League Presents: The Reluctant African, 1961 September 24; AV492; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 492)
  - Urban League Presents: Employing the Handicapped Worker, 1961 October 1; AV493; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 13:30 (Box 12, Reel 493)
  - Urban League Presents: Townsend Harris and Free Education, 1961 October 9; AV494; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 494)
    Related materials
  - Urban League Presents: Housing Violations, 1961 October 16; AV495; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 495)
  - Urban League Presents: How to Look for a Job, 1961 October 23; AV496; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 496)
  - Urban League Presents: Does Language Hamper Racial Understanding?, 1961 October 30; AV497; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 497)
    This recording may have also been broadcasted on WWRL, a radio station located in New York City.
  - Urban League Presents: Are Present School Boycotts the Answer?, 1961 November 6; AV498; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 498)
  - Urban League Presents: Inside Angola, 1961 November 26; AV499; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 499)
  - Urban League Presents: The Disgrace of New York's Migrant Labor, 1961 December 3; AV500; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 500)
  - Urban League Presents: What Does Africa Really Want From Us?, Part I, 1961 December 10; AV501; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 501)
  - Urban League Presents: What Does Africa Really Want From Us?, Part II, 1961 December 18; AV502; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 502)
  - Urban League Presents: The Dilemma of the Negro Writer, part 1, 1961 December 25; AV503; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 503)
  - Urban League Presents: The Dilemma of the Negro Writer, part 2, 1962 April 8; AV504; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 504)
  - Urban League Presents: Echoes of Africa, 1962 April 16; AV505; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 505)
  - Urban League Presents: Worker Exploitation, Part I, 1962 April 23; AV506; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 506)
  - Urban League Presents: Worker Exploitation, Part II, 1962 April 29; AV507; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 507)
  - Urban League Presents: Can Mayor's Contract Compliance Program Work?, part 1, 1962 May 7; AV508; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 12, Reel 508)
  - Urban League Presents: Can Mayor's Contract Compliance Program Work?, Part 2, 1962 May 13; AV509; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 15:00 (Box 123, Reel 509)
  - Urban League Presents: A Growing Crisis in the City's Welfare Program, 1962 May 20; AV510; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 123, Reel 510)
  - Urban League Presents: Has Housing Integration Come to the Upper West Side?, 1962 May 28; AV511; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 123, Reel 511)
  - Urban League Presents: What is AMSAC's Mission?, 1962 June 3; AV512; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 13:00 (Box 123, Reel 512)
  - Urban League Presents: The Young Citizens, 1962 June 11; AV513; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 513)
  - Urban League Presents: Your Rights When Arrested, 1962 June 24; AV514; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 514)
    This recording may have also been broadcasted on WNJR, the college radio station for Washington and Jefferson College in Washington, Pennsylvania.
  - Urban League Presents: How to Land a Job in the Foreign Service, part 1, 1962 July 1; AV515; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 515)
  - Urban League Presents: How to Land a Job in the Foreign Service, Part 2, 1962 July 9; AV516; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 516)
  - Urban League Presents: The Blacks, 1962 July 16; AV517; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 517)
  - Urban League Presents: Problems of Installment Buying ("Buying on Credit"), 1962 July 22; AV518; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 518)
    This tape is related to materials in RG 39.5, Records of WNYU (Radio Station: New York, N.Y.).This tape is related to materials in RG 39.5, Records of WNYU (Radio Station: New York, N.Y.).
  - Urban League Presents: How to Apply for Public Housing, 1962 July 29; AV519; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 519)
  - Urban League Presents: A Business with a Social Purpose, 1962 August 6; AV520; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 520)
  - Urban League Presents: A Minute of Your Time, 1962 August 13; AV521; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 audiocassettes Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 521)
  - Urban League Presents: The Compulsive Drinker, 1962 August 19; AV522; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 522)
    Alcoholism.
  - Urban League Presents: Bedford-Stuyvesant Looks to Psychiatric Needs, 1962 August 27; AV523; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 523)
  - Urban League Presents: Social Action in Education, 1962 September 3; AV524; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 524)
  - Urban League Presents: Unmarried Mothers, 1962 September 9; AV525; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 525)
  - Urban League Presents: A Report on School Dropouts, 1962 September 17; AV526; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 15:00 (Box 13, Reel 526)
  - Urban League Presents: Is More Training the Answer to Better Social Service?, 1962 September 23; AV527; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 527)
  - Urban League Presents: The Bible and Race Relations, Part 1, 1962 September 30; AV528; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 13:00 (Box 13, Reel 528)
  - Urban League Presents: The Bible and Race Relations, Part 2, 1962 October 7; AV529; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 529)
  - Urban League Presents: How Can School Dropouts Succeed?, part 1, 1962 October 14; AV530; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 530)
  - Urban League Presents: How Can School Dropouts Succeed?, part 2, 1962 October 22; AV531; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 531)
  - Urban League Presents: The Concluding Part of a Special Series on How Can the School Dropouts Succeed?, 1962 October 29; AV532; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 532)
  - Urban League Presents: The Long Shadow of Little Rock, 1962 November 4; AV533; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 533)
  - Urban League Presents: Haryou (A New Harlem Youth Project), 1962 November 18; AV534; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 13, Reel 534)
  - Campus Editorial: Does the Current Trend in Popular Music Tend to Promote Juvenile Delinquency?, 1956; AV542 (Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 21, Box 13, Reel 542, Item 61)
  - Campus Editorial: Is the Quality of TV Programs Improving?, 1956; AV543 (Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 22, Box 13, Reel 543)
  - Campus Editorial: Will We Have a Third World War?, 1956; AV544 (Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 23, Box 13, Reel 544, Item 60)
  - Viewpoint International: Religions in Russia, 1956; AV545 (Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 24, Box 13, Reel 545)
    Russia.; Religion
  - Campus Editorial: Supreme Court Judicial Review, 1956; AV546 (Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 25, Box 13, Reel 546)
  - Urban League Presents: A Program for School Integration, Part 3, 1960; AV548 (Box 13, Reel 548)
  - Urban League Presents: Parents in Public School Life, 1960; AV549 (Box 13, Reel 549)
  - Urban League Presents: Myths of Racial Discrimination, Part 1, 1960; AV550 (Box 13, Reel 550)
  - Urban League Presents: Myths of Racial Discrimination, Part 2, 1960; AV551 (Box 13, Reel 551)
  - Urban League Presents: Myths of Racial Discrimination, Part 3, 1960; AV552 (Box 13, Reel 552)
  - Urban League Presents: Myths of Racial Discrimination, Part 4, 1960; AV553 (Box 13, Reel 553)
  - Urban League Presents: The Death of Africa, 1960; AV554 (Box 14, Reel 554)
  - Urban League Presents: Democratic Program for Civil Rights, 1960; AV555 (Box 14, Reel 555)
  - Urban League Presents: A Republican Program for Civil Rights, 1960; AV556 (Box 14, Reel 556)
  - Urban League Presents: A Priest Looks at Harlem's Problems, Part 1, 1961 January 1; AV565; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 14, Reel 565)
    Harlem (New York, N.Y.)
  - Urban League Presents: A Priest Looks at Harlem's Problems, Part 2, 1961 January 8; AV566; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 14, Reel 566)
  - Urban League Presents: Let's Get Rid of Rats, 1961; AV567 (Box 14, Reel 567)
  - Urban League Presents: Untitled, 1961; AV568 (Box 14, Reel 568)
  - Urban League Presents: Can You Afford a Co-op Apartment?, Part 1, 1961 December 31; AV569; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.); 1 sound tape reels Approx. 14:30 (Box 14, Reel 569)
  - Urban League Presents: The Reluctant African, 1961; AV1399 (Box 36, Reel 1399)
  - Urban League Presents: A Rabbi Looks at Bigotry, 1959; AV1451 (Box 38, Reel 1451)
  - Urban League Presents: Racial Discrimination in Music, 1959; AV1452 (Box 38, Reel 1452)
  - Urban League Presents: A Renewal Program for Harlem, 1959; AV1453 (Box 38, Reel 1453)
  - Urban League Presents: The Role of Youth, 1959; AV1454 (Box 38, Reel 1454)
  - Urban League Presents, 1959; AV1455 (Box 38, Reel 1455)
  - Urban League Presents: The Metcalf-Baker Fair Housing Bill (Part 1), 1959; AV1456 (Box 38, Reel 1456)
  - Urban League Presents: The Metcalf-Baker Fair Housing Bill (Part 2), 1959; AV1457 (Box 38, Reel 1457)
  - Urban League Presents: A Priest Looks at Bigotry, 1959; AV1458 (Box 38, Reel 1458)
  - Urban League Presents: Progress for the Negro Worker, 1959; AV1459 (Box 38, Reel 1459)
  - Urban League Presents: A Psychiatrist Looks at Bigotry (Part 1), 1959; AV1460 (Box 38, Reel 1460)
  - Campus Editorial: Federal Aid to Education, 1956 February 10; AV1474 (Box 38, Item 1474, Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 26)
  - Campus Editorial: Is Education For All, Education For None?, 1956 February 12; AV1475 (Box 39, Item 1475, Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 27)
  - Campus Editorial: What Does the Election Mean to Me?, 1956 November 4; AV1476 (Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 28, Box 39, Item 1476)
  - Viewpoint International: The Social and Political in Italy, 1956 February 19; AV1478 (Box 39, Item 1478, Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 29)
  - Viewpoint International: Spanish Folklore, 1956 May 6; AV1479 (Box 39, Item 1479, Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 30)
  - Viewpoint International: Folk Music of Spain, 1956 February 10; AV1480 (Box 39, Item 1480, Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 31)
  - Viewpoint International: What are elections like in your country?, 1956 November 4; AV1481 (Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 32, Box 39, Item 1481)
  - Viewpoint International: French Literary Life, 1956 March 4; AV1482 (Box 39, Item 1482, Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 33)
  - Viewpoint International: The French Novel Today, 1956 February 12; AV1483 (Box 39, Item 1483, Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 34)
  - Viewpoint International: The Influence of Spanish Culture on the United States, 1956 March 25; AV1484 (Box 39, Item 1484, Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 35)
  - Viewpoint International / Campus Editorial: Institute for International Education: What is the Nature of our Foreign Policy?, 1956 March 10; AV1485 (Box 39, Item 1485, Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 36)
  - The Irish Muse: An Evening of Readings New York University Producer: Elisa Guarino, 1993 April 27; AV1679; Guarino, Elisa; 1 VHS (Box 44, Cassette 1679)
  - Richard Nixon Resignation (Tape 1 of 2), 8 August 1974; AV1848; 1 Half_Inch_Video_Reel (Box 155, Reel 1848)
    This recording includes the complete resignation speech of former U.S. President Richard Nixon, as well as clips from NBC, CBS, and ABC news coverage of the event.
    Provenance
    This recording was donated by the Office of Media Production.
    Original format: 1/2 inch open reel video; Transfer Technician Notes: "This tape contains news segments prior to, during, and after Richard Nixon's resignation, as well as a brief documentary on his rise to the presidency. All segments suffer from moderate to severe generational loss, notably heavy image echo. The documentary section exhibits inherent dirt, dust, and scratches from the original film source. There are frequent dropouts and tape wear during the content, and occasional tape damage. Occasional sync errors occur, with some segments suffering from a pronounced skew error. Severe audio buzz and hiss throughout, and audio distortion are all inherent to the original recording."
    Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994
  - Richard Nixon Resignation (Tape 2 of 2), 8 August 1974; AV1849; 1 Half_Inch_Video_Reel (Box 155, Reel 1849)
    This recording includes footage of Richard Nixon during his presidency, as well as interviews with Bella Abzug, Gabe Pressman, and New York University School of Law Dean Robert McKay. It also includes footage of Gerald Ford being sworn in as Vice President, and the appointment of Henry Kissinger as Secretary of State.
    Original format: 1/2 inch open reel video; Transfer Technician Notes: "This tape contains news segments during the aftermath of Richard Nixon's resignation and the presidential appointment of Gerald Ford. Content includes several documentary segments that exhibit inherent dirt, dust, and scratches from original film source(s). All segments suffer from moderate to severe generational loss, notably heavy image echo. There are frequent dropouts and tape wear during the content, and occasional tape damage. Occasional sync errors occur, with some segments suffering from a pronounced skew error. Occasional jitter occurs. Severe audio buzz and hiss throughout, and audio distortion are all inherent to the original recording."
    Abzug, Bella S., 1920-1998; Ford, Gerald R., 1913-2006; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994
  - Community councils--informational, 1981 May 5; AV1850 (Box 48, Item 1850)
  - Taking the Right Steps: A Guide to Career Planning and Placement (master), 1987; AV1851 (Box 48, Item 1851)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst memorial service (tape 1 of 2), undated; AV1852 (Box 48, Item 1852)
    Bobst, Elmer Holmes
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst memorial service (tape 2 of 2), undated; AV1853 (Box 48, Item 1853)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst memorial service (tape 1 of 2, backup), undated; AV1854 (Box 48, Item 1854)
    Baker, Elmer E., 1922-
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst memorial service (tape 2 of 2, backup), undated; AV1855 (Box 48, Item 1855)
  - Conversation with Harold Hudson Channer (Group W Cable Vision Systems), 1983 August 24; AV1856 (Box 48, Item 1856)
    Scope and contents
    Frank Ferrell may also appear on this video. Originally broadcast by the Manhattan and Group W Cable Vison systems in New York City Wednesday, August 24, 1983, at 11:00 pm.
    Brademas, John, 1927-2016
  - Cutbacks in student aid (WCBS-TV news), undated; AV1857 (Box 48, Item 1857)
  - Straight Talk (WOR TV), 1985 October 2; AV1858 (Box 48, Item 1858)
  - Lecture: Moshe Dayan (Great Speakers Series) (tape 1 of 3), 1974 November 4; AV1859; Dayan, Moshe, 1915-1981 (Box 48, Item 1859)
  - Lecture: Moshe Dayan (Great Speakers Series) (tape 3 of 3), 1974 November 4; AV1861; Dayan, Moshe, 1915-1981 (Box 49, Item 1861)
  - Lebost space age windmill/wind turbine (edited), undated; AV1862 (Box 49, Item 1862)
    This tape may depict a windmill atop the Barney Building.
  - First Huntley Memorial Award presentation (tape 2 of ?), undated; AV1865 (Box 49, Item 1865)
    This tape is related to RG 46.8, Records of the Presentation of University Awards.
  - Second Huntley Memorial Award presentation (tape 1 of 2), undated; AV1866 (Box 49, Item 1866)
  - Second Huntley Memorial Award presentation (tape 2 of 2), undated; AV1867 (Box 90, Item 1867)
  - Lecture: Moshe Dayan (Great Speakers Series) (tape 2 of 3), 1974 November 4; AV1860; Dayan, Moshe, 1915-1981 (Box 48, Item 1860)
  - Ireland House Dedication (Original), 26 April 1993; AV1968 (Box 50, Cassette 1968)
    General note
    3 1142 04655057 3